
[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "엄마 돈 많아?",
        "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "엄마 차 있어?",
        "difficulty": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "인생이란 무엇인가",
        "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "강아지 vs 고양이",
        "difficulty": 0
    },
    {
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다1",
        "timestamp": 1683752902,
        "id": 168375
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다123",
        "comment": "코멘트입니다1211",
        "answerTime": 1681210902,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다2-코멘트 있음",
        "timestamp": 1681200902,
        "id": 168120
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다3",
        "answerTime": 1681978502,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다3-코멘트 없음",
        "timestamp": 1681958502,
        "id": 168195
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다4",
        "answerTime": 1682496902,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다4",
        "timestamp": 1682496902,
        "id": 168249
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다5",
        "answerTime": 1682410502,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다5",
        "timestamp": 1682410502,
        "id": 168241
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다6",
        "answerTime": 1682324102,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다6",
        "timestamp": 1682324102,
        "id": 168232
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다7",
        "answerTime": 1682237702,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다7",
        "timestamp": 1682237702,
        "id": 168223
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다8",
        "answerTime": 1682147702,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다8",
        "timestamp": 1682147702,
        "id": 168214
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다9",
        "answerTime": 1682057702,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다9",
        "timestamp": 1682057702,
        "id": 168205
    },
    {
        "answer": "답입니다10",
        "answerTime": 1683101702,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "질문입니다10",
        "timestamp": 1683101702,
        "id": 168310
    }
]
